<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rodriguez_Ruiz_Francisco_Jose_PMDM02</string>

    <string-array name="super_mario_characters">
        <item>Mario</item>
        <item>Luigi</item>
        <item>Princess Peach</item>
        <item>Bowser</item>
        <item>Yoshi</item>
        <item>Toad</item>
        <item>Wario</item>
        <item>Donkey Kong</item>
        <item>Koopa Troopa</item>
        <item>Goomba</item>
        <item>Princess Daisy</item>
        <item>Rosalina</item>
        <item>Toadette</item>
        <item>Waluigi</item>
        <item>Kamek</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="super_mario_titles">
        <item>Hero of the Mushroom Kingdom</item>
        <item>Mario's brave brother</item>
        <item>Princess of the Mushroom Kingdom</item>
        <item>King of the Koopas</item>
        <item>Mario's loyal dinosaur ally</item>
        <item>Servant of Princess Peach</item>
        <item>Mario's greedy rival</item>
        <item>King of the Jungle</item>
        <item>Bowser's turtle soldier</item>
        <item>Common enemy of the Mushroom Kingdom</item>
        <item>Princess of Sarasaland Kingdom</item>
        <item>Guardian of the Stars</item>
        <item>Adventurer and Toad’s friend</item>
        <item>Luigi's jealous rival</item>
        <item>Bowser's wizard servant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="character_traits">
        <item>Mario, brave, main hero, great jumper, plumber</item>
        <item>Luigi, shy, Mario's brother, great jumper, loyal</item>
        <item>Princess Peach, elegant, ruler of Mushroom Kingdom, kind, frequently kidnapped</item>
        <item>Bowser, evil, king of the Koopas, strong, obsessed with Peach</item>
        <item>Yoshi, loyal, dinosaur, long tongue, carries characters</item>
        <item>Toad, helpful, Mushroom Kingdom resident, brave, fast</item>
        <item>Wario, greedy, Mario's rival, strong, seeks riches</item>
        <item>Donkey Kong, powerful, banana lover, strong, protector of his island</item>
        <item>Koopa Troopa, classic enemy, shell, can be thrown, Bowser's army member</item>
        <item>Goomba, small, common enemy, armless, easy to defeat</item>
        <item>Princess Daisy, energetic, ruler of Sarasaland, cheerful, Peach's friend</item>
        <item>Rosalina, mysterious, cosmic guardian, serene, cares for Lumas</item>
        <item>Toadette, cheerful, Toad's friend, adventurous, helps heroes</item>
        <item>Waluigi, vengeful, Wario's companion, tricky, agile</item>
        <item>Kamek, wizard, Bowser's ally, uses magic, cunning</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="super_mario_descriptions">
        <item>The protagonist of the saga, a brave and friendly plumber always ready to save the Mushroom Kingdom and rescue Princess Peach from Bowser’s clutches.</item>
        <item>Mario's younger brother, known for his loyalty and courage, though often shy. He often joins Mario in adventures to save the Mushroom Kingdom.</item>
        <item>The ruler of the Mushroom Kingdom, constantly kidnapped by Bowser. Peach is kind and elegant but has also proven to be a fighter on several occasions.</item>
        <item>The main antagonist of the series, Bowser is the fearsome king of the Koopas, obsessed with conquering the Mushroom Kingdom and marrying Princess Peach.</item>
        <item>Mario's faithful companion, a green dinosaur who uses his tongue to catch enemies. Yoshi helps Mario in many of his missions throughout the saga.</item>
        <item>A resident of the Mushroom Kingdom, loyal servant of Princess Peach. He often assists Mario by offering advice and help on his adventures.</item>
        <item>An old enemy of Mario, now more known for his greedy personality and constant pursuit of wealth and power. Wario is Mario’s rival but also embarks on his own adventures at times.</item>
        <item>The king of the jungle and an occasional ally of Mario. Donkey Kong is known for his great strength, love of bananas, and rivalry with King K. Rool.</item>
        <item>One of Bowser’s soldiers, Koopa Troopa is a turtle who commonly appears as an enemy in Mario games but can also be a playable character or ally in other installments.</item>
        <item>A small mushroom-shaped enemy of the Mushroom Kingdom, often the first opponent Mario encounters in many games. Despite their size, they can be dangerous in large numbers.</item>
        <item>The princess of Sarasaland and a close friend of Princess Peach. Daisy is known for her energetic and competitive personality, often participating in sports and races.</item>
        <item>A powerful guardian of the stars and mother of the Lumas. Rosalina plays an important role in protecting the cosmos and is a mysterious character with great wisdom.</item>
        <item>An adventurer and Toad’s friend who shares his enthusiasm for exploration. Toadette has proven to be a brave companion in many missions and appears in numerous games.</item>
        <item>Luigi’s rival and nemesis, Waluigi is known for his mischievous personality and constant quest for recognition. Although never a main antagonist, he’s a recurring character in sports and party games.</item>
        <item>A powerful wizard serving Bowser, often posing a major obstacle to Mario and his friends. Kamek uses magic to make missions harder by transforming enemies into more dangerous forms.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>